Guide to the George Borchardt Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II
  - English Language Publishers and Agents
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Unsworth, Mair (Box 114)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Valdes, Ivy (Box 114)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Village London. (Box 114)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Walder, David (Box 114)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Walk in Dread. Anthology (Box 114)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Walsh, Arthur Edward & John Paxton (Box 114)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Walsh, Sheila (Box 114)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Walters, John (Box 114)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Weaver, Bill & Keith Macklin (Box 114)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Weldrick, Valerie (Box 114)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: White, Eric Walter (Box 114)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Whittle, Norah (Box 114)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Wilson, Mary (Gladys Mary Baldwin Wilson, Baroness Wilson of Rievaulx) (Box 114)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Wood, James (Box 115)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Woodward, Edward (Box 115)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Wrightson, Patricia (Box 115)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: The Year's Art series (Box 115)
    - Hope Leresche & Sayle Literary & Dramatic Agents, 1966-1969 (Box 115)
    - Hope Leresche & Sayle, 1970-1975 (Box 116)
    - Hope Leresche & Sayle, 1976 (Box 117)
    - Hope Leresche & Sayle: Aveline, Claude (Box 118)
    - Hope Leresche & Sayle: Beeching, Jack "James Barbary" (Box 118)
    - Hope Leresche & Sayle: Bloom, Leonard (Box 118)
    - Hope Leresche & Sayle: Brown, Phil (Box 118)
    - Hope Leresche & Sayle: Ellis, William (Box 118)
    - Hope Leresche & Sayle: Hogarth, Paul (Box 118)
    - Hope Leresche & Sayle: James, John "David John" (Box 118)
    - Hope Leresche & Sayle: McGough, Roger (Box 118)
    - Hope Leresche & Sayle: Marshall, Archibald (Box 119)
    - Hope Leresche & Sayle: Miskin, Lionel (Box 119)
    - Hope Leresche & Sayle: Park, Ruth (Box 119)
    - Hope Leresche & Sayle: Rule, Jane (Box 119)
    - Hope Leresche & Sayle: Schuster, Felicia & Cecilia Wolseley (Box 119)
    - Hope Leresche & Sayle: Usine-Universite-Union (Box 119)
    - David Machin (London International; A.P. Watt & Son) De Bono, Edward, 1968 & 1969 (Box 120)
    - David Machin (London International; A.P. Watt & Son) Hamilton, Elizabeth, 1968 & 1969 (Box 120)
    - London Magazine Editions, 1969-1978 (Box 120)
    - The Odyssey Press, 1970 (Box 120)
    - Laurence Pollinger Limited Authors' Agents, 1961, 1962, 1968 (Box 120)
    - Laurence Poilinger Limited 1970-1975 (Box 121)
    - Henry Regnery Company Pubiishers, Chicago 1953-1954 (Box 121)
    - Deborah Rogers Ltd Literary Agency 1970-1973 (Box 121)
    - Neville Spearman Limited Publishers 1959, 1965, 1966 (Box 121)
    - Neville Spearman Limited Publishers 1967-1973 (Box 122)
    - Neville Spearman Limited Publishers 1974-1976 (Box 123)
    - Neville Spearman Limited Publishers Hutton, J. Bernard (Box 123)
    - Neville Spearman Limited Publishers Lonsdale, Gordon A. (Box 123)
    - Neville Spearman Limited Publishers Pollini, Francis (1) (Box 123)
    - Neville Spearman Limited Publishers Pollini, Francis (2) (Box 124)
    - Vallentine, Mitchell & Co. Ltd.: Ben-Gurion, David (Box 124)
    - Vallentine, Mitchell & Co. Ltd.: Dan, Ben (Ben Porat & Uri Dan) (Box 124)
    - Vallentine, Mitchell & Co. Ltd.: Melnikoff, Pamela Rita (Box 124)
    - Vallentine, Mitchell & Co. Ltd.: Parkes, James (Box 124)
    - Vallentine, Mitchell & Co. Ltd.: Vernon & Copeman Ltd., 1966-1969 (Box 124)
    - Vallentine, Mitchell & Co. Ltd.: Vernon & Copeman Ltd.: Seago, J.H. (Box 124)
    - George Weidenfeld & Nicolson Limited 1964 (Box 124)
    - George Weidenfeld & Nicolson Limited Chastel, Andre (Box 124)
    - George Weidenfeld & Nicolson Limited Pathfinder series of biographies (Box 124)
    - George Weidenfeld & Nicolson Limited Wide World Lecture Bureau (Box 124)
  - French Language Authors, Publishers and Agents
    - Aubier Editions Montaigne Casterman S.A. Editeurs, Tournai, Belg. (Box 125)
    - Delachaux & Niestle S.A. Neuchâtel, Switz. (Box 125)
    - Les Editions Denoël (Box 125)
    - Les Editions Denoël Gonthier Planete, 1962-1966 (Box 125)
    - Denoël Sauvy, Alfred (Box 125)
    - Editions Desclee de Brouwer S.A. Bruges, Belg. (Box 125)
    - DDB Publishers, Inc. New York (Box 125)
    - Esprit (Box 126)
    - L'Express (Box 126)
    - Flammarion et Cie (Box 126)
    - Librairie Ernest Flammarion (Box 126)
    - Laure Forestier Agent Litteraire (Box 126)
    - Editions Gallimard (Box 127)
    - Librairie Gallimard, 1955-1962 (Box 127)
    - Gallimard, 1963-1966 (Box 128)
    - Editions Gonthier Societe Nouvelle des Editions Gonthier (Box 128)
    - Editions Bernard Grasset, 1963-1965 (Box 128)
    - Grasset, 1966-1967 (Box 129)
    - Rene Julliard Editeur Editions Rene Julliard, 1963-1966 (Box 129)
    - Editions Robert Laffont, 1962-1966 (Box 129)
    - Michelle Lapautre Literary Agent, 1966-1982 (Box 130)
    - Michelle Lapautre, 1978 (Box 131)
    - Editions de Miriuit: Textbook edition (Box 131)
    - Monteilhet, Hubert (Box 131)
    - Mossinsohn, Igal (Box 131)
    - Fernand Nathan Editeur; Librairie Fernand Nathan & Cie (Box 131)
    - Nedoncelle, Maurice (Box 131)
    - Oceana Publications, New York (Box 131)
    - Ouvaroff, Serge Traducteurs Litteraires (Box 131)
    - Editions de Paris (Box 131)
    - Philip, Andre (Box 131)
    - Librairie Plon, 1954-1960 (Box 132)
    - Plon, l96l-1962 (Box 133)
    - Plon: Bassan, Jean (Box 133)
    - Plon: Baton, Mikios (Bajom Mikios) (Box 133)
    - Plon: Bourbon-Parme, Prince Xavier de (Box 133)
    - Plon: Chailly, Jacques (Box 133)
    - Plon: Cuenot, Claude (Box 133)
    - Plon: Daninos, Pierre (Box 133)
    - Plon: D'un monde a 1'autre series (Box 133)
    - Plon: Favrod, Charles-Henri (Box 133)
    - Plon: Carder, Michel (Box 133)
    - Plon: Gaulle, Charles de (Box 133)
    - Plon: Guerdan, Rene (Box 133)
    - Plon: Hell, Henri (Box 133)
    - Plon: Katcha, Vahe (Box 133)
    - Plon: Laborde, Jean (Box 133)
    - Plon: Latil, Pierre de & Jean Rivoire (Box 133)
    - Plon: Mammeri, Mouloud (Box 134)
    - Plon: Mauriac, Francois (Box 134)
    - Plon: Montherlant, Henri de (Box 134)
    - Plon: Paleologue, Maurice (Box 134)
    - Plon: Rivoyre, Christine de (Box 134)
    - Plon: Senet, Andre (Box 134)
    - Plon: Spens, Willyde (Box 134)
    - Plon: Troyat, Henri (Box 134)
    - Plon: Victor, Paul Emile (Box 134)
    - Plon: Yourcenar, Marguerite (Box 134)
    - Editions du Pont Royal, 1961-1962 (Box 134)
    - Pont Royal: Histoire de la magie (Box 134)
    - Pont Royal: L'Hormne et l'animal (Box 134)
    - Pont Royal: Rome (Histoire de Rome et des Romains) (Box 134)
    - Presse-Avenir, 1961-1962 (Box 135)
    - Presse-Avenir Flaceliere, Robert (Box 135)
    - Les Presses de la Cite, 1962 (Box 135)
    - Presses Universitaires de France, 1954-1962 (Box 135)
    - Editions du Rocher, Monaco, 1956-1957; 1965-1966 (Box 135)
    - Editions du Rocher Barral, Louis (Box 135)
    - Romero, Luis (Box 135)
    - Rossignol, Jean, 1964-1969 (Box 135)
    - Roy, Jules, 1966-1968 (Box 135)
    - Editions Seghers, 1961-1962 (Box 135)
    - Seghers: Rossif, Frederic & Madeleine Chapsal (Box 135)
    - Societe des Auteurs et Compositeurs Dramatiques (Box 136)
    - Strassova Agency: Maurois, Michelle (Box 136)
    - Strassova Agency: Marceau, Felicien (Box 136)
    - La Table Ronde (Box 136)
    - Les Editions de la Table Ronde, 1953-1970 (Box 136)
    - La Table Ronde: Cabanne, Pierre (Box 136)
    - La Table Ronde: Lazareff, Helen & Pierre Telihard de Chardin (Box 136)
    - Editions Pierre Tisne Librairie Laurent Tisne, 1955-1969 (Box 137)
    - Editions Pierre Tisne Architecture series (Box 137)
    - Editions Pierre Tisne Napoli (Box 137)
    - Editions Pierre Tisne Henry Regenery Company. Publishers (Box 137)
    - Trez, Alain (Box 137)
    - Editions Universitaires (Box 137)
    - Vauthier, Jean, 1960-1963 (Box 137)
  - Other Foreign Rights and Agents
    - Agencia Literaria Carmen, Balcells (Barcelona), 1972-1977 (Box 138)
    - Alexander Gans Literair Agent, (Noordwijk aan Zee, The Netherlands), 1963-1979 (Box 138)
    - Japan UNI Agency, Inc (Tokyo), 1970-1977 (Box 139)
    - Linder AG Literary Agency, Zurich, 1969-1973 (Box 139)
    - Linder, Erich (Box 140)
    - Agenzia Letteraria Internazionale, Milan, 1970-1977 (Box 140)
    - Mohrbooks Literary Agency Rainer Heumann, Zurich, 1974-1976 (Box 140)
    - Reca Media Services, Ltd. Tel Aviv, l974-1975 (Box 140)
    - Lennart Sane Agency, Malmö, Sweden, 1969-1978 (Box 141)
    - Charles E. Tuttle Co., Inc. Tokyo, 1970-1977 (Box 141)
- Series III:
  - English Language Authors
    - Adams, Jane (Box 142)
    - Armstrong, Gregory (Box 142)
    - Azerrad, Jacob (Box 142)
    - Arzin, Nathan (1) (Box 142)
    - Arzin, Nathan (2) (Box 143)
    - Barrett, Paul (Box 143)
    - Beiser, A & G (Box 143)
    - Belkin, Madeline (Box 143)
    - Bell & Weinstein (Box 143)
    - Benedikt, Michael (Box 144)
    - Benson, Dennis (Box 144)
    - Berg, Barbara (Box 145)
    - Berman, Marshall (Box 145)
    - Bing, Elizabeth (Box 145)
    - Birnbaum, Ben (Box 145)
    - Black, Elizabeth (Box 145)
    - Bluestone, Naomi (Box 145)
    - Botsford, Keith (Box 146)
    - Bowers, John (Box 146)
    - Boyd, Blanche (Box 146)
    - Bridges, Sue Ellen (Box 146)
    - Broat, I. G. (Box 147)
    - Brolin, Brent (Box 147)
    - Burland, Brian (Box 147)
    - Caine, Paul (Box 148)
    - Carlisle, Olga (Box 148)
    - Chase, James Hadley (Box 148)
    - Cohen, Arthur (Box 148)
    - Colman, Libby & Arthur (Box 148)
    - Connell, Maureen (Box 148)
    - Coppola, Eleanor (Box 148)
    - Cornfield, Robert (Box 148)
    - Cruz, Victor (Box 148)
    - Cunliffe, Mitzi (Box 148)
    - Danto, Arthur (Box 149)
    - de Bono, Edward (Box 149)
    - Denham, Alice (Box 149)
    - Dennison, George (Box 149)
    - Diamond, Stanley (Box 149)
    - Drexler, Rosalyn (1) (Box 149)
    - Drexler, Rosalyn (2) (Box 150)
    - Dunkell, Samuel (Box 150)
    - Eady, Toby (Box 150)
    - Edison, Russell (Box 150)
    - Eisler, Riane Tennenhaus (Box 150)
    - Ettinger-Chodakowska, Elizabeta (Box 150)
    - Fackenheim, Emil (Box 151)
    - Farber, Joseph (Box 151)
    - Fenisong, Ruth (Box 152)
    - Fisher, Elizabeth (Box 152)
    - First, Elsa (Box 152)
    - Flam, Jack (Box 152)
    - Flender, Harold (Box 152)
    - Freedman, Ralph (Box 152)
    - Friedman, Maurice (Box 152)
    - Furst, Jeffrey (Box 152)
    - Gardner. John (1) (Box 153)
    - Gardner, John (2) (Box l54)
    - Gavin Thomas (Box 155)
    - Gaylin, Willard (Box 155)
    - Geissbuhler, E (Box 155)
    - Gerassi, John (Box 155)
    - Gilliatt, Penelope (Box 156)
    - Goffstein, M (Box 156)
    - Gold, Ivan (Box 157)
    - Goldbeck, Nikki & David (Box 157)
    - Goldberg, Gerald Jay (Box 157)
    - Goldberger, Paul (Box 158)
    - Goldstein, Joyce (Box 158)
    - Goldstein, Richard (Box 158)
    - Goldstein, Ruth (Box 158)
    - Goldwaithe, John (Box 158)
    - Goodell, Rae (Box 158)
    - Gordon, Diana R (Box 159)
    - Gordon, Suzanne (Box 159)
    - Greiff, Constance (Box 159)
    - Gross, Leonard (Box 159)
    - Grow, Judith (Box 159)
    - Guston, Philip (Box 159)
    - Hammer, Signe (Box 159)
    - Hanley, William (Box 160)
    - Harrison, Barbara (Box 160)
    - Harrison M. (Box 160)
    - Haskell, Molly (Box 161)
    - Henderson, David (Box 161)
    - Hendin, Herbert (Box 161)
    - Hendin, Josephine (Box 161)
    - Israel, Peter (Box 161)
    - Jacoby, Susan (Box 162)
    - Jarnow, Jill (Box 162)
    - Johnson, Charles (1) (Box 162)
    - Johnson, Charles (2) (Box 163)
    - Johnson, Edgar (Box 163)
    - Johnston, Jill (Box 163)
    - Jones, D. F. (Box 163)
    - Katz, Jacob (Box 164)
    - Katz Steve (Box 164)
    - Kay, Mara (Box 164)
    - Keeley, Edmund (Box 165)
    - Kluger, Richard (Box 165)
    - Knowler, John (Box 165)
    - Koning, Hans (Box 166)
    - Kovier, Peter (Box 166)
    - Kuhns, William (Box 166)
    - Kurzweil, Edith (Box 167)
    - Lahr, John (Box 167)
    - Landon, H.C Robbins (Box 167)
    - Larson, Charles (Box 167)
    - Lawner, Lynne (Box 168)
    - Lebowitz, Albert (Box 168)
    - Lenzer, Gertrude (Box 168)
    - Levin, Meyer (1) (Box 168)
    - Levin, Meyer (2) (Box 169)
    - Lyndoe, Edward (Box 169)
    - Mackinnon, Charles (Box 169)
    - Mainwaring, Marion (Box 170)
    - March, Stella (Box 170)
    - Millett, Kate (Box 170)
    - Molinaro, Ursule (1) (Box 170)
    - Molinaro, Ursule (2) (Box 171)
    - Moorse, George (Box 171)
    - Morgan, Robin (Box 171)
    - Noel, Thomas (Box 172)
    - Padfield, Peter (Box 172)
    - Pollin, Francis (Box 172)
    - Pugh, Derek (Box 172)
    - Rogers, Anthony (Box 172)
    - Roth, Henry (1) (Box 172)
    - Roth, Henry (2) (Box 173)
    - Steiner, Robert (Box 173)
  - English Language Publishers, Agents, and Subjects
    - American Motion Pictures (Box 173)
    - American Publishers 1919-1980 (Box 173)
    - Bernheim, Alain (Box 173)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: General files, 1911, 1913-1915 (Box 173)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Correspondence, 1976 (Box 174)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Allison, Sonia (Box 174)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Banks, Lynne Reid (Box 174)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Beeching, Wilfred (Box 174)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Bell, Gerard (Box 174)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Blair, Peter Hunter (Box 174)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Cauthery, Philip & Cole, Martin (Box 174)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Emenyonu, Ernest (Box 174)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Enright, D.J. (Box 174)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Gilbert, Anna (Box 174)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Glaskin, G.M. (Box 175)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Gussman, Boris (Box 175)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Heffron, Doris (Box 175)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Herley, Richard (Box 175)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Howse, Derek (Box 175)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Huggett, Richard (Box 175)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Kettle, Pamela (Box 175)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Koch, Christopher J. (Box 176)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Lefebure, Molly (Box 176)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd LeMarchand, Elizabeth (Box 176)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Longmate, Norman (Box 176)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Macksey, Kenneth (Box 177)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Mercier, Vivian (Box 177)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Merry, Bruce (Box 177)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Money, Keith (Box 177)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Moss, Robert (Box 177)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Osbourne, Helena (Box 177)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Partington, Norman (Box 177)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Price, Jeramie (Box 177)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Rayson, Steven (Box 178)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Robinson, Gail (Box 178)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Rowdon, Maurice (Box 178)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Segal, Muriel (Box 178)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Shulman, Sandra (Box 178)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Stuart, Forbes (Box 178)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Trevor, Meriol (Box 178)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Turner, Philip (Box 179)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Ware, Jane & Hunt, Hugh (Box 179)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Wheeler, Guy (Box 179)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd White, Alan (Box 179)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd White, Celia (Box 179)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Wilson, Cohn (Box 180)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Wilson, Sandra (Box 181)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Wordsworth, Jill (Box 181)
    - British Publishers: -- --Agreements -- --General, 1971 - 1977 (Box 181)
    - Cape Ltd Correspondence, 1975/6, 1977 (Box 182)
    - Cape Ltd Alpers, Anthony (Box 182)
    - Cape Ltd Bailey, Paul (Box 182)
    - Cape Ltd Bargate, Verity (Box 182)
    - Cape Ltd Clarke, I.F. (Box 182)
    - Cape Ltd Collinson, Peter (Box 182)
    - Cape Ltd Dibdin, Michael (Box 182)
    - Cape Ltd Dixon, Norman (Box 182)
    - Cape Ltd Heinz & Lee (Box 183)
    - National Trust (Box 183)
    - Offerings, 1976, 1917 (Box 183)
    - Cape Ltd. Plomer, William (Box 184)
    - Cape Ltd. Rowse, A.L. (Box 184)
    - Cape Ltd. Suyin, Han (Box 184)
    - Cape Ltd. Von Mises, Ludwig Chapman & Hall (Box 184)
    - Chapman & Hall Feakes (Box 184)
    - Fiction Collective (Box 184)
    - Green Ltd Literary Agency Caute, David (Box 184)
    - Green Ltd Literary Agency Caute, John (Box 184)
    - Hale, Robert, Ltd. (Box 185)
    - Harrel, Anne Literary Agency (Box 185)
    - Hart-Davis Hill, Brian (Box 185)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Ltd Aitchinson, Jean (Box 185)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Ltd. Alder, Vera Stanley (Box 185)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Ltd. Andrews, Alan (Box 185)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Ltd. Ashford, Jeffrey (Box 185)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Ltd. Audemars, Pierre (Box 185)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Ltd. Barrie and Jenkins - General (Box 185)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Ltd. Beare, George (Box 185)
    - Hutchinson Ltd: Brandon-Jones, David (Box 186)
    - Hutchinson Ltd: Crawley, Aileen (Box 186)
    - Hutchinson Ltd: Forsyth, Frederick (Box 186)
    - Hutchinson Ltd: Friendly, Alfred (Box 186)
    - Hutchinson Ltd: Germany, Jo (Box 186)
    - Hutchinson Ltd: Greene, Liz (Box 186)
    - Hutchinson Ltd: Grender, Iris (Box 186)
    - Hutchinson Ltd: Gribble, Leonard (Box 186)
    - Hutchinson Ltd: Griffiths, Helen (Box 186)
    - Hutchinson Ltd: Griffiths, Kenneth (Box 186)
    - Hutchinson Ltd: Hale, James (Box 186)
    - Hutchinson Ltd: Hardy, Alister (Box 186)
    - Hutchinson Ltd: Harvie, Robert (Box 186)
    - Hutchinson Ltd: Koestler, Arthur (Box 186)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Harris, Harold (Box 187)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Hayes, Horace (Box 187)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Raynes, Renee (Box 187)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Hetiderson, Ian (Box 187)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Hickin, Norman (Box 187)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Hill, Grahm (Box 187)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Hobbs, William (Box 187)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Hodson, Harry (Box 187)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Holland, Lillie (Box 187)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Honeycombe, Gordon (Box 187)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Hopkins, Jeffrey & Sopa, Geshe (Box 187)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Hosking, Eric (Box 188)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Howells, Roscoe (Box 188)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Howlett, John (Box 188)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Howson, Gerald (Box 188)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Hoyle, Sir Fred (Box 188)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Hubank, Roger (Box 188)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Hulke, Malcom (Box 188)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Humanities (Box 188)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Hutchinson, Alan (Box 188)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Huxley, Ann (Box 188)
    - Hutchinson Ltd John Paul II, Pope (Box 189)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Knox, Bill (Box 189)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Lister, Margot (Box 189)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Muskett, Peter (Box 189)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Netherclift, Beryl (Box 189)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Prentis, Evelyn (Box 189)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Reeman, Douglas (Box 189)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Rendell, Ruth (Box 189)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Renier, Elizabeth (Box 189)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Robin, Bernard (Box 189)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Santa-Maria, Jack (Box 189)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Stewart, Bruce (Box 190)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Strong, Michael (Box 190)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Thorpe, Sylvia (Box 190)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Trollope, Joanna (Box 190)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Unsworth, Mair (Box 190)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Walsh, Sheila (Box 190)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Watson, Peter (Box 190)
    - Hutchinson Ltd Wrightson, Patricia (Box 190)
    - Justice Department (Box 190)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle: Marevna (Box 190)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle: Mockler, Anthony (Box 190)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle: Nott, Kathleen (Box 191)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle: Rothenstein, Sir John (Box 191)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 191)
    - Mitchell, Valentine: Horbach, Michael (Box 191)
    - Mitchell, Valentine: Jacobs, Louis (Box 191)
    - Mitchell, Valentine: Rabinowitsch, Wolf Z. (Box 191)
    - Mitchell, Valentine: Reitlinger, Gerald (Box 191)
    - Mitchell, Valentine: Rubens, Alfred (Box 191)
    - Mitchell, Valentine: Samuel, Lord Edwin (Box 191)
    - Muller Frederick (Box 191)
    - Rivers Press: Drieau La Rochelle (Box 191)
    - Rogers, Deborah Ltd, Literary Agency (Box 191)
    - Routledge & Kegan Paul Ltd, 1916, 1977 (Box 192)
    - Routledge & Kegan Paul Ltd Dinsdale, Tim (Box 192)
    - Routledge & Kegan Paul Ltd Foremans, Michael (Box 192)
    - Routledge & Kegan Paul Ltd Rulledge, Dom Denys (Box 192)
    - Sidgwick: Martucci & Ranieri (Box 192)
    - Sidgwick: Moussa, Pierre (Box 192)
    - Sidgwick: Rab, Gustav (Box 192)
    - Simon, Richard Scott Ltd, l973-l974 (Box 192)
    - Simon, Richard Scott Ltd, 1975-1978 (Box 193)
    - Simon, Richard Scott Ltd G-M, 1979-1980 (Box 194)
    - Simon, Richard Scott Ltd Correspondence, 1972, 1976, 1979-1980 (Box 194)
    - Simon, Richard Scott Ltd Fleetwood, Hugh (Box 194)
    - Simon, Richard Scott Ltd General, 1972-1974 (Box 194)
    - Simon, Richard Scott Ltd Gilbert, Harriet (Box 195)
    - Simon, Richard Scott Ltd Glazebrook, Philip (Box 195)
    - Simon, Richard Scott Ltd Heald, Tim (Box 195)
    - Simon, Richard Scott Ltd Kenyon, Michael (Box 195)
    - Simon, Richard Scott Ltd Offerings (retired), 1972-1975 (Box 195)
    - Simon, Richard Scott Ltd Offerings (retired), 1976-1980 (Box 196)
    - Simon, Richard Scott Ltd Slaughter, Carolyn (Box 195)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Correspondence, 1977 (Box 195)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Barbault, Armand (Box 195)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Bashkiroff, Zenaide (Box 197)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Bass, Virginia (Box 197)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Bender, Albert (Box 197)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Bowen, Charles (Box 197)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Boy Who Saw True (Box 197)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Brother Philip (Box 197)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Burr, Harold Saxton (Box 197)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Burton, Richard (The Perfumed Garden) (Box 197)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Colquhoun, Ithell (Box 197)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Crawford, Sheilagh (Box 197)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Dickie, James (Box 197)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Drake, Raymond (Box 197)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Furst, Jeffrey (Box 197)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: General (Box 197)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Gibbons, Gavin (Box 197)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Goncourt, Edmond (Box 197)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Haining, Peter (Box 198)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Howson, J.B. (Box 198)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Hutchinson, Beryl (Box 198)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Junke, N. (Box 198)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: King, Francis (Box 198)
    - Spearman, Neville Ltd: Lyndoe, Edward (Box 198)
    - Spearman Ltd Mathers, S. Macgregor (Box 198)
    - Spearman Ltd Meacock, Norma (Box 198)
    - Spearman Ltd Milner & Smart (Box 198)
    - Spearman Ltd O'Hara, Patrick (Box 198)
    - Spearman Ltd Ravenscroft, Trevor (Box 198)
    - Spearman Ltd Rudorff, Raymond (Box 199)
    - Spearman Ltd Russell, Edward (Box 199)
    - Spearman Ltd Ryall, Edward (Box 199)
    - Spearman Ltd Sadoul, Jaques (Box 199)
    - Spearman Ltd Shores & Ring (Box 199)
    - Spearman Ltd Snelling, O.F. (Box 199)
    - Spearman Ltd Tchernine, Odette (Box 199)
    - Spearman Ltd Thorne, Edward (Box 199)
    - Spearman Ltd Trench, Brensley Le Poer (Box 199)
    - Spearman Ltd Wade, E.G. (Box 199)
    - Spearman Ltd Walton, Alan Hull (Box 199)
    - Spearman Ltd Whore (Box 199)
    - Spearman Ltd Williamson, George Hunt (Box 199)
    - Spearman Ltd Youth Hosteller's Guide to Europe (Box 199)
    - Vernon, Victoria Ltd, Authors' Agents 1971-1972, 1976 & 1977 (Box 199)
    - Vernon, Victoria Ltd, Authors' Agents Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 199)
    - Vernon, Victoria Ltd Butterworth, Michael (Box 200)
    - Watt, A,P. & Son Aldiss, Brian (Box 200)